What's your department?
Com Arts.
Com Arts? It's fun there.
Nero likes people from Com Arts.
We're making things awkward for Florence.
No, Owen, it's okay.
Besides, I'm not fond of the Ferells,
but Nero, you already have an advantage.
Because if there's someone you like
from Com Arts Department,
I can act as a bridge.
There's someone I like.
What's the problem
with that Jennilyn Mercado,
I mean, Jenny.
Well, it's because
someone is sending her secret messages.
What's the problem?
Should she talk to the person
and ask why he's doing that?
Why is he sending her messages
if he has a secret motive?
And what I can advise you is,
don't confront him yet.
Give him time
and eventually,
he will have the courage to face you
and tell you what he truly feels for you.
I want you to cook Chopsuey for me.
Is that all? No problem.
It's just a small thing.
You will be needing
freshly picked vegetables,
because that's how Dona Ferell used to do it.
You can go to the farm
early morning, tomorrow.
From what I heard,
our produce is ready for harvest.
I'll ask Nero to drive you.
What?
You assume too much, Florence.
Who do you think you are? Jennilyn Mercado?
Are you that beautiful
for him to have secret feelings for you?
What are you thinking, Florence?
You're not going on a date with Nero.
You'll just go to the farm.
Why are you so concerned about your outfit?
What's happening to you, Florence?
Let's play some music.
Don't you want to sing?
I'm out of tune.
It's not important if you're in tune or not.
What's important is...
you're beautiful.
Let's go.
The doves.
Hey, hey, get out!
Get out of there!
This way, hurry! Get out!
They don't want to go out!
Go!
You two, get out! Let's go!
Let's go!
The picture.
Hurry!
Hurry, the fire is getting bigger!
Move back, move back!
- Watch out, watch out!
- Water!
- Did anyone bring a phone?
- Call the fire department!
- Call the firemen!
- Water!
- Did anyone bring a phone?
- The water is running out!
- What happened to my cabin?
- Hey, Nero, Nero!
- My things! Let me go!
- Nero!
- We can't do anything!
- You don't understand!
My things are important to me! My cabin!
- Stay here!
- Let me go!
- Nero!
- My things!
- Stop it, Nero!
- You don't understand!
- Let me go! My cabin!
- It's dangerous!
- Nero!
- Stop it, Nero!
Stop it!
Why do you have this?
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
All of a sudden there was fire.
Nero, just calm down.
Let's find out first what happened.
Maybe all of this is just an accident.
This woman destroyed a place
that's very important to me.
How can I calm down?
Tell me how can I calm down?
I'm sure Florence didn't mean to do this.
Hey Owen, stop it first.
It's not the time to take sides.
What Owen is saying
is don't jump to conclusions.
Maybe Florence has an explanation for this.
You too.
Stop it! Everyone should stop
and please, everyone, go inside.
We'll talk about this
when everyone has calmed down,
so we'd know the root of this mess.
Believe me, Grandpa,
even if I have calmed down,
I don't want to see the face of this woman.
So please, kick her out, Grandpa.
You better rest, Florence.
We'll talk about this tomorrow
so we can think clearly about this.
Ouch!
Why?
I have a bad feeling.
Something wrong is happening.
Go and call Florencia.
Hello, my child.
Why don't you have a camera?
I'm in the bathroom, Mother, Father,
making number 2.
Florence, have you given the rambutan?
Did the kids like it?
Yes, Mother, Father.
He liked it very much
and consumed everything.
He ate a lot.
Florence, you're lying.
Go and turn on the camera.
What?
Father, I'm telling the truth.
Florencia, show yourself.
Mother, Father...
Nero, so you're here.
I asked Dencio to look for you,
but we can't find you.
Where did you go?
By the way,
Florence was saying something about the...
Sorry to interrupt, Don Ferell,
Florence said she turned on the lights.
And something suddenly sparked.
No one is maintaining the cabin.
That's the thing.
But what is she doing in my cabin?
She has no right to go in there.
I agree.
That was Florence's fault.
She did not respect your privacy.
But grandson,
the reason she did it
is because she wants to surprise you.
When she found out that you like rambutan,
she asked her parents
to look for rambutan for you.
Why are you defending her, Grandpa?
The truth is...
despite what happened, I admire her bravery.
She had the guts to reach out to you
and be your friend,
not like your Grandpa
who became a coward to approach you,
and left you all alone.
The fact that she discovered your secret camp
is very impressive.
It means, she's not only cooking for you,
she's making an effort to get to know you.
I'm sorry, grandson,
I won't agree to kick Florence out.
I think it's time we learn to forgive...
because if we don't know how to forgive,
we will not have a heart
deserving of happiness
and capable of love.
Resign?
Yes.
That's what my parents and I
have agreed upon.
I committed a huge sin against you.
It would be a hassle on your part
if one of your grandsons is mad at me.
He might lose his appetite
and refuse to eat if he sees me here.
So you mean instead of
asking for forgiveness,
you'll just run away from your mistake?
In other words,
you are evading responsibility.
Your mistake wasn't done intentionally.
Everything was an accident.
I think I made a mistake
with my impression of you, Florence.
No, I'm very responsible
when it comes to my actions,
and this is what I think
is the responsible thing to do.
To face the consequences of
the actions that I made.
What do you think, Serafica?
I'm so disappointed, Sir.
But I agree with you, Don Ferell,
resigning is just an excuse
to avoid responsibility for her mistakes.
There are just two people
that I hate in this world.
The people who don't know how to
cross the street in the pedestrian lane,
and the people who don't know
how to apologize.
As in...
I'm sorry.
I'll make a deal with you.
Apologize to Nero first.
Now, if he can't forgive you, then resign.
I will even give you
a generous separation pay.
But don't give up easily.
Try it first.
Give the people a chance to forgive.
Do not underestimate
our power of forgiveness.
As the saying goes,
we all deserve a second chance.
Apologize to Nero first.
Do not underestimate
our power of forgiveness.
As the saying goes,
we all deserve a second chance.
Not everyone deserves a second chance.
Why, does Hitler deserves a second chance?
Me, I deserve a second chance.
What are you doing here?
Didn't I tell you
I don't want to see you anymore?
Hey, wait.
I'm sorry.
One minute... that's all I ask from you.
Just one minute.
You have every right to get mad at me.
I shouldn't have followed you that night.
I shouldn't have watched you talk and dance
with your doves.
But you made me curious,
you were off to the woods in the dark.
What will you do there?
Who knows if you're a vampire or worse,
you'll hunt for a unicorn
and then you will drink their blood.
That's because you're a bit weird.
But what I did was wrong
because my curiosity is not valid enough
to invade your privacy, right?
And in our world,
no one is respecting our privacy.
So I know that your space is important
so you'll feel safe.
That's where you feel safe,
and you can be who you want to be.
Thirty seconds.
But the truth is,
I just want to make up
for all the kindness you did for me.
I know that sometimes... you defend me.
If you're enjoying yourself
at the expense of others,
that's not called fun.
You call that being disrespectful.
Who are you? Are you her boyfriend?
Hey!
I also know your vote of confidence
in my cooking.
What do you think of Florence's home cooking?
I like her.
I mean, I like her cooking.
And I also know your effort to cheer me up
so I'd feel good about myself.
It's you again.
You even woke me up.
Don't get tired of dreaming.
I also know the saying,
"the road to hell is paved
with good intentions",
but that's what I only want.
For me to be able to make it up
for all the kindness you did for me.
I'm sorry that I burned your bat cave.
I hope when our paths cross again,
you will no longer be mad at me.
And you can see me as the person
who only wants to make it up
for all your kindness.
Thanks for the one minute.
You have every right to get mad at me.
I shouldn't have followed you that night.
I shouldn't have watched you
talk and dance with your doves.
But you made me curious,
you were off to the forest in the dark.
What will you do there?
Who knows if you're a vampire or worse,
you'll hunt for a unicorn
and then you will drink their blood.
That's because you're a bit weird.
But what I did was wrong
because my curiosity is not valid enough
to invade your privacy, right?
And in our world,
no one is respecting our privacy.
So I know that your space is important
so you'll feel safe.
That's where you feel safe
and you can be who you want to be.
Thirty seconds.
But the truth is...
I just want to make up
for all the kindness you did for me.
I know that sometimes... you defend me.
Who are you? Are you her boyfriend?
Hey!
I also know your vote of confidence
in my cooking.
I like her.
I mean, I like her cooking.
And I also know your effort to cheer me up
so I'd feel good about myself.
What is she saying,
that I'm making her feel good?
I also know the saying,
"the road to hell is paved
with good intentions",
but that's what I only want.
For me to be able to make it up
for all the kindness you did for me.
I'm sorry that I burned your bat cave.
I hope when our paths cross again,
you will no longer be mad at me.
And see me as the person
who only wants to make it up
for all your kindness.
My wish is,
I hope the time will come
when you won't feel
something lacking in your life.
But when that day comes,
I hope you'll meet someone
who will knock on your heart.
That's my prayer.
Son, let her in.
So she'd know who the real you is.
What if he really refused to let you in?
I will just keep on knocking...
Knock, knock, knock, until he opens the door.
If he doesn't want to open the door,
I'll destroy it!
If I need to sneak into the sidelines
or peep out the window
so he'd let me in, I'll do it.
If I need to shout, I will shout.
Hey, let me in your heart!
Is she the kind of person you were saying,
who will come into my life, Dad?
Troy.
I heard Grandpa Garp is making
Florence apologize to Nero.
You think Nero will forgive her?
I don't think so, because knowing Nero,
he's one of the toughest guys that I know.
Well, knowing Florence,
she can be quite persuasive
especially when she starts
talking from her heart.
Let's make a bet.
Okay.
As for Owen and I, game.
What are we betting on this with?
I'll bet my car.
Well, you wanted to switch cars, anyways.
Game.
Me? I'll bet the Rolex
that Mom gave me as a gift.
Okay, give me your Rolex and your car too,
you won't win anyway.
- Let's see about that.
- That's true!
Let's see who will win.
Mr. Dove?
Forgiveness is an expensive gift.
Not everyone deserves it.
Is he saying I don't deserve his forgiveness?
Does it mean he is capable of forgiving
but he refused to give that to me?
Your boss is too harsh, Mr. Dove.
Let me answer him.
[Forgiveness is an expensive gift.
Not everyone deserves it.]
I spoke to him earlier,
but it seems he's still mad at me.
And based on the message he sent earlier,
it looks like
that fool can no longer forgive me.
And, Mother, that's the deal
I made with Grandpa Garp.
If his grandson can't forgive me,
I will just go home.
But Grandpa Garp said that
if I will really go home,
he is still willing
to continue my scholarship.
Mother, Father, I'll just call again later.
It looks like Grandpa Garp is asking for me.
Bye.
Love you both.
Nero?
I accept your apology...
But there's a condition.
Condition?
You owe me.
How much?
Do I need to pay for your cabin?
I don't need your money.
Huh?
So what do I owe you?
You owe me three P's.
Three P's?
Human Development Program of the government?
Or Public-Private Partnership?
No.
What I mean is, you owe me three favors.
Three favors?
Yes.
When the time comes
that I need a favor from you,
you can't turn me down.
No questions asked.
You will help me with the favor
I'll be asking you.
What kind of favor?
Anything.
As in anything?
Yes...
Anything and any time.
That should be enough replacement
for what you've burned,
and all the sins you've committed.
All the sins?
It's as if I've done a lot of bad things
to you.
You don't want?
Deal.
Yes, Nero?
For the first favor, come with me.
Where are we going?
Have you forgotten?
Because of what you did,
you owe me three favors.
No questions, and you can't turn it down.
So when I say come with me, you'll go.
Where are we going?
Well...
Let's go.
For the second favor you'll do for me,
can you dance with me?
Wow.
And for the last favor, I'll ask from you...
Kiss me.
Kiss me with love.
What?
What did you get yourself into, Florence?
Three favors and you agreed?
What if he asks for...
Erase, erase, erase...
Don't think of bad things, Florence.
Besides, you won't agree
to do rated SPG favors.
Stop it, Florence,
just focus on your job today.
Focus on your job.
Thanks for your forgiveness.
Why is she saying thank you?
Am I disturbing you?
You're playing with your bird again?
I'm sorry, Bro, I just can't help it.
It's like a fruit from a tree.
It's like a low-hanging fruit
with you and your doves in your room.
Do you need anything?
Nothing much.
I was just surprised by what I discovered.
So this is what you do
whenever you go missing.
You're taking care of birds?
Exactly.
I thought you were doing something
whenever you were alone.
So you made the playroom made by Uncle Nilo
into your bat cave.
Nice bat cave, Bro.
It's actually very cool.
Too bad, it got burned.
And to think of it, whenever you go missing,
Aldus and I made a theory
that you transformed into a werewolf
and looked for a victim at night.
- Right Aldus?
- Yeah.
You can't blame us, Bro.
If your cabin hadn't burned down,
we wouldn't know
about this cool hobby of yours.
How can you do this?
Are you like Robert Downey Jr?
Wait, does Ironman have pet doves?
No, It's not Ironman.
It's the movie where he knows
how to talk to animals.
Ah, Stuart Little.
That's not Stuart Little,
it's Doctor Dolittle.
Doctor Dolittle.
It's the one
where he knows how to talk to animals.
I think that's the one.
So you know how to talk to doves?
Tweet, tweet.
Not just doves,
but maybe with different kinds of animals too.
What are you talking about?
I can't talk to doves, and I'm not Ironman.
Relax, Bro, no one is calling you Ironman.
Ironman.
But it's still pretty cool that
you're taking care of a lot of birds.
Yes, is that a superpower?
I think you're eligible
to apply as an Avenger.
Birdman.
You don't need superpowers
to take care of doves.
They are very intelligent,
and it's easy to teach them.
Really?
What's that?
I use them to send messages.
Really?
- Yes.
- So they can do that?
But the important question is,
to whom do you send messages using your pet?
Yes.
From what it looks like,
it's someone special.
What are you talking about?
If you don't need anything, you can go.
Hey, where are you going?
- Stop touching your birdie.
- Come here, Birdman.
Hey.
Is there anything else you want us to do,
Don Ferell?
No more. We're fine.
By the way, you and your staff can eat.
Thank you, Sir.
- Serafica?
- Yes, Sir?
Can Florence join us for dinner?
No thank you, Grandpa Garp.
You might discover that I eat a lot of rice.
Don't be ridiculous, Florence.
Of course,
she'll be honored to join you, Sir.
Very good.
- Join us.
- Yes, I'll be honored to join you.
Come on.
Florence, why don't you join us?
Okay.
Excuse me, Sir.
You don't have a knife.
And you don't have drinks.
Okay, eating time.
Wait.
Won't we pray first?
Sorry, I'm just used to doing that at home,
but if you don't practice that here,
that's okay.
You might be from a non-sectarian family.
No, no, no. We're not non-sectarian.
Go ahead, it's a good idea actually
if we pray now.
Will you do the honors to lead the prayer?
Sure, no problem.
Good.
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit,
Amen.
Thank you, Lord, for the food
and the chance for us to eat together now.
But there are a lot of things
I am thankful for, not only for the food.
Thank you that everybody who is eating here
is safe and healthy.
Thank you
that we're not infected with the virus
that can affect our sense of taste.
But most importantly,
thank you to the Ferell Family
who accepted me.
That even if sometimes I failed,
they were able to forgive me.
And now, I was invited to eat with them.
You're really great, Lord,
so thank you so much.
And if saying thank you is kage bunshin...
Thank you times two, times two,
times two, times two.
Never-ending thank you to you, Amen.
There.
So, can we eat?
- Game.
- Okay.
You won't eat rice?
Grandpa.
In two seconds, can you give ten fruits
that start with the letter F?
F?
One, two... Time is up.
There's no fruit
that starts with the letter F.
Fruit salad.
Boom.
- Cheating.
- Boom.
Work smarter, not harder.
You're so funny.
You inherited that from your father.
I'll take that as a compliment, Grandpa.
You should.
You shouldn't be ashamed of your father.
How about you, Florence?
How are you? Are you ready for school?
Yes. Tomorrow is my day off,
and I'll be meeting my mother and father.
For what?
We'll buy things for school,
and I can also give my first salary to them
for father's medications.
Good girl.
By the way, send my regards to your parents.
You know, they're very lucky to have you,
and tell them that the family is very happy
because you made us happy with
the nice food that you're preparing for us.
My regards.
Yes. Do you know that
I always talk about you?
I hope everyone likes to tell a story.
Not like our brother over there.
He has so many secrets.
Grandpa, do you know about his birds?
Yes, the doves...
His father taught him how to teach the birds.
Now, did you know that
it was me who taught his father?
But not only that, Grandpa.
- Huh?
- Nero's the romantic type.
He's using the birds to send secret messages.
Secret messages?
Busted.
So, Nero, who is this
special someone of yours?
That's none of your business.
Stop bugging Nero.
Anyway, let's just wait.
Give him time and space,
I'm sure one of these days,
we'll find out who is that secret girl
and what are the messages.
Right, Nero?
Maybe longer.
Birdman.
Longer time.
Guys, have you noticed Owen?
Why?
He's becoming close to Florence.
I can see that as well.
Do you think something is going on with them?
Huh, that's weird.
Remember, it was he who said
it's totally unacceptable
if we fall for the cook.
Guys, here we go again.
After we bully Florence,
now we're thinking badly of her?
She deserves some credit.
Ever since she became our cook,
Grandpa Garp seems happy,
and we look like a family that eats together.
What I can only say, Bro,
you got to give her a chance.
And once you get to know her,
you'll see how fun she is to be with.
Honestly, I'm okay with her.
I'm starting to like her.
Like her?
As in, like her?
Of course not.
What I mean is,
I'm starting to appreciate the good things
she's doing here at home.
Not to mention that she does cook well.
How about you, Aldus?
So, Nero,
who is this special someone of yours?
Of course, he won't admit
who his special someone is.
It's just me.
What will they think if they found out
that he has fallen for a cook?
Wait, just because I'm a cook,
a Ferell is not allowed to like me?
Because we're worlds apart?
In the drama series,
the lead characters from different worlds
always fall for each other.
But it's a drama series
because it's not for real.
Is it my fault that I'm not rich?
Did I like that?
And I don't want to be rich.
The richer you are,
the more problems you have.
And I'm happy with the kind of life I have.
I will never replace Mother and Father
for a luxurious life.
Hello?
Hello, Don Rogelio, Sir.
This is Mark.
I've already run the aging program
that I told you about,
the picture of Baby Celestina.
I emailed you a picture
of how she will possibly look in 17 years.
All right.
Thank you.
He will bring me to school?
- Yes.
- No need, Ma'am Serafica.
Grandpa Garp has helped me a lot.
I can go to school on my own,
so I won't disturb you and Mr. James.
I'm rooting for you.
Good luck.
Point me in the right direction.
Or better yet,
make our paths meet so I can save her,
and give her the life you dreamed for her.
Please, Alyanna.
Break a leg and see you at school.
I'm Florence Dela Cruz
and I'm going to school.
What in the name of...